(Leonard:)No,
(Raj:)Sheldon's right.
(Raj:)Emily did say I always
(Raj:)talk about my feelings too much.
I-I suppose that
(Sheldon:)could be a legitimate
concern in a relationship.
(Sheldon:)Uh, perhaps even
a-a red flag.
(Sheldon:)And speaking
of red flags,
(Sheldon:)check out this sexy number
from the former Soviet Union.
(Sheldon:)Hubba, hubba.
(phone ringing)
(Amy:)Oh. Uh, we-we have
another caller.
(Amy:)Hi. You're on
Fun with Flags.
KRIPKE: Hello. I want to talk
about how lonely I am, too.
(Raj:)Kripke? Is that you?
(Barry:)Yeah, I'm just sitting here
all by myself
wondering if I'll ever find
someone to share my life with.
Preferably Asian, 18-24,
no fatties.
(Sheldon:)Please, all comments
and questions
(Sheldon:)should be flag-related.
All right. Is my pole
flag-related?